Hello everyone, we are Frog House
Rome.
The messy home environment can actually be improved from some small places.
Today, we have compiled more than 30
quick storage techniques for kitchens, refrigerators, and wardrobes.
A list of recommended storage items will also be listed. yo
Friends who haven’t subscribed
before reading,
remember to subscribe first and turn on the little bell.
Many people think that the kitchen is the big devil when storing
ingredients, dry goods, kitchen utensils,
large and small , and there are
so many things in various shapes. Integrate and classify things
such as soy sauce, rice wine, etc. Bottles and cans
can be stored in this file box from MUJI.
The seasoning jars are very high and easy to pour up and down. Put
the sauce jars in the file box
without worrying about the mess of the bottles and jars. It’s
just as easy to hold and more tidy
if you use multiple file boxes with
bottles and cans in a tall and deep drawer like this.
This narrow storage box
can be freely combined at a 90-degree right angle.
The narrow type is convenient to put in the cabinet
. Storage cups
are a headache in the kitchen. Seasoning jars
are neatly in place.
The bagged brewed drinks are placed in a higher cabinet
because it is inconvenient to take.
You can use this storage basket with handles to facilitate dragging and picking.
Storage boxes with handles
are suitable for placing in deeper and higher places.
With handles, it is convenient to pull
items placed in high places for access, and it is also convenient
to put bottles and cans inside.
Pull the storage box to take items,
which is convenient and neat.
The storage basket with handles is in the It is sold in Daiso or general hardware department stores.
Powder ingredients can be supported in the cabinet
with telescopic rods and S hooks or long-tail clips
to hang items. Opened ingredients
can be clipped with clips and hung in
a bag. The cabinet is very neat and tidy
. When it is relatively high,
the space below can also be matched with a storage box
to store more items.
This narrow box for storing bottles and cans
has grooves on the side,
which is very suitable for standing dishes or pots and
pans. Put the handle outward to
get more It is convenient
to use tools to store kitchen utensils.
Standing upright will save space.
The storage of bowls and plates is also the same principle.
If the plane space is limited,
you can
use a file storage box
to put the plates upright
.
There is no need to move the plates around.
A plate rack with a mouth shape like this
is a good tool for upright storage of dishes.
The front end has a rubber pad, which is not afraid of hurting the plates.
One plate rack can store about 6 or 7 plates,
and it looks like a bookshelf. There are card slots at the bottom of
this L-shaped plate rack.
It is quite stable.
One plate rack can hold about 6 plates.
Because it is very stable, the lid of the pot will not fall down.
Yideli This storage rack is also very easy to use.
The storage rack has Large and small
plates of different sizes have places to store them.
In addition,
the telescopic rod is also a very practical tool for storage.
As long as two telescopic rods are used, it can be used as a partition to store
the plates.
Use the telescopic rod to separate the space like this
. Plates and cutting boards can be stored upright
and picked up more conveniently.
I often don’t know where to put the bulky pot lid?
Recommend this Yideli vertical pot cover, which
can correspond to pots with a size of 26 to 30 cm.
The handle of the pot cover can be placed upright
and standing, so you don’t have to worry about the pot cover when you don’t know where to
put
it
. The middle of the lid is made of glass,
so you can clearly see the changes in the ingredients in the pot.
The lid is very light, and the handle is large and easy to hold. It
is suitable for pots of different widths.
This is a smart and good product for the kitchen.
You will never regret buying it.
Kitchen cutlery drawer Various tools So much
how to organize it?
In the drawer, you can use MUJI’s PP finishing box to store it.
First, empty the drawer completely.
The finishing method is the same.
At the same time, make a big
classification and reclassify tableware and kitchen
utensils
separately
. The easy-
to-empty drawer arranges PP organizers of various sizes.
Chopsticks, knives, forks, and spoons
are sorted in medium-sized organizers.
Small measuring cups and sauce bowls
are stored together in small square ones.
Long-shaped organizers
store soup spoons separately. Long cooking utensils
are easier to hold.
Finally, put the cooking scissors
at the front of the drawer and put
away the kitchen utensils that were stuffed together in the drawer.
Find a place to put them back. The drawer is clean and tidy.
The point is that you can find everything you need immediately when cooking
There are 1-4 different sizes of MUJI finishing boxes.
The systematic design
can be freely combined and matched.
Taiwan brand KEYWAY Baolai series
has 1-6 different sizes.
The appearance of the white matte surface
is very similar to that of MUJI.
The height is a little higher and
the price is cheaper.
Both of these are recommended to buy.
In addition, there is this Yideli telescopic tableware organizer
that can be adjusted according to the size of the drawer. The size of the organizer
can be adjusted both vertically and horizontally
because it can be pulled on both sides
to fit drawers of different depths and sizes.
Put it vertically and horizontally. It is easy to use
the partition of the box to store different tableware separately
. Chopsticks, spoons and other tableware are placed separately for easier access.
Are the organized drawers much neater?
The practicality is quite high.
If the space in the kitchen is limited,
you can use two telescopic rods and add a piece of mesh
to make a useful counter storage rack.
Tie the mesh to the telescopic rod with a drawstring
to form a small storage rack
for things. You can use the straps to tie it to the mesh,
or you can buy a hanger for the mesh,
which is more convenient to install.
Put the storage rack on
the top of the kitchen to withstand the bottom of the system cabinet
and support it on the countertop.
After the shelf is stable, it is a practical way to make full use of the wall. The storage rack
is equipped with S hooks to hang kitchen utensils. The
storage rack can be used to place seasonings, etc.
neatly and easily.
Don’t waste the space on the side of the refrigerator.
Baoya has many Japanese inomata storage boxes.
These three storage boxes are
long and magnetic. There is a hook on the bottom
for pens and paper tape.
If you don’t have a labeling machine,
you can use paper tape to write on the label.
This magnetic box can store all your tools. It’s
horizontal and convenient to put a small sauce bag.
You can also put garlic and other ingredients. The ventilated square
shape is very suitable for small drawers.
Classify and store rubber bands, sealing clips and other small items.
All the magnetic suction is on the side of the refrigerator
for easy access. It is convenient to use
under the kitchen countertop. It is easy to accumulate sundries if you are not careful.
Because there are drainage pipes,
there is usually no shelf
. Use storage boxes and shelves to separate them
. This space can be effectively used
and turned into a useful storage space.
The width of this counter shelf
can be freely expanded
and the height can be adjusted according to needs, which can
make more effective use of space.
The assembly of the shelf is very simple.
Just lock the nut.
If the water pipe is not If it is convenient to draw it up,
install the shelf in the cabinet.
Lock one side
and put it in the cabinet, and then lock the other side.
The shelf is movable
and can be installed flexibly according to the position of the
water pipe on the counter.
It is very easy to
install this two-tiered storage drawer,
just install the poles
and put the movable storage box
on the drawer track
The height of the
drawer design
cabinet will not be wasted
The storage box with wheels is easy to drag and drop.
The
seasoning jars on the countertop
are more organized than the colorful packaging.
Using a uniform bottle body can make the countertop more tidy.
This is often seen in the kitchen of storage masters. There are
two sets of four with shelves.
Open powder cans and oil tanks with
thick sealing strips.
Put on seasonings and plug tightly.
When using, slide the lid open
and operate with one hand. It is very convenient
to store in a unified way.
If you want to reduce the accumulation on the countertop, you can also use magnetic suction.
There are two large and small boxes. The opening
capacity is 60ml, which can fill a can of small mill seasoning.
The tightness is close enough
to stick to the label sticker, and then
it is magnetically attracted to the side of the refrigerator
or fixed on the wall with a strong magnetic strip.
It is easy to use without wasting any space.
The oil in the large can is also convenient. It can be packaged separately.
This jar of oil and vinegar is inconspicuous
but very practical.
The glass bottle
is slender and easy to hold.
The appearance is very beautiful.
After the oil and seasoning are packaged,
you can also label it to distinguish
the bottle. The stopper is very sealed.
The bottle can be opened by tilting the lid,
and the oil will be poured out very smoothly
. It will not pour out too much at one time. It
is very good
to control the amount of oil
and no oil will flow out
of the bottle mouth
. Chain bags and heat-resistant bags can be used to store shrimp skins in drawable storage boxes. You can
buy them in three sizes: S, M, and L. They
are all copper plate products.
Fold them along the creases and
put them into the support plate and heat-resistant bag.
Then you can pull them out from the middle opening.
You can also write or stick labels.
Whether it is a heat-resistant bag, a fresh-keeping bag, or a garbage bag,
it is super neat and tidy
. How to classify and store garbage bags of different sizes?
The soft and collapsed garbage bags are very suitable for organizing with file boxes.
A4 file hanger
with double hook design is suitable for hanging on MUJI file boxes.
The garbage bags can be sorted, folded and
hung in different sizes.
You can also label and indicate the size of
messy garbage bags.
Easy to classify
, easy to extract, easy to use
, just take the size you need every time, and
reduce the time of rummaging
. Easy to extract and clean.
If it is a recycled plastic bag,
you can use a large zipper bag
and use a card to draw a square on the zipper bag.
Use a knife to cut a square access opening
, fold the plastic bag
and put it in the zipper bag
to take out the garbage bag. It is very convenient
to hang this garbage bag storage bag on the kitchen door
to get the garbage bag more easily.
I want it to be easier.
You can also cut an open plastic bag
directly at the bottom of the zipper bag
and put it in the zipper bag
with a drawer from the bottom
, which is also very convenient.
Let’s take a look at the inside of the refrigerator.
A messy refrigerator is easy to find things
. I will forget the ingredients in the deep part of the refrigerator
and put the food in the expired
refrigerator for storage. The most important thing is to manage the ingredients well
so that the food can be kept fresh effectively to eat healthy.
Fresh-keeping boxes are the best tools for storing ingredients.
Foodstuffs stored in crisper boxes
can not only keep fresh It lasts longer.
The crisper can be stacked
so that the refrigerator space can be used more thoroughly.
It is very convenient to use the crisper for food preparation and storage.
Vegetables should be washed and cut the day before cooking,
put in the crisper and
refrigerated.
Foodstuffs
can be placed in fresh-keeping boxes or fresh-keeping bags, and then frozen. The fresh
-keeping boxes and fresh-keeping bags
can be washed and reused repeatedly.
The size of the fresh- keeping box
is also very important.
Large and small can be used to classify and store different ingredients.
It is recommended to buy the same series of stackable crispers.
Usually, fresh-keeping boxes of the
same brand and
style are
better stacked
because
the specifications
are consistent
It is more effective
and not afraid to put the expired
ingredients. Use the crisper to store the ingredients.
The transparent crisper makes the contents in the box clear at a glance. It is easier to find
the refrigerator and it is tidy and clean.
In addition, the flat crisper can be stacked
with a storage basket and stand upright.
The lid of the crisper is closely connected to the body. High fit,
upright storage, not afraid of pouring it out.
To save the time of cooking every day,
you can cut the vegetable ingredients first.
Like this, prepare all the vegetables in the fresh-keeping box
and put them in the refrigerator.
When cooking, pull out the storage box
to find the ingredients.
There are also a lot of sauce bottles and cans in the refrigerator.
Using this narrow and long storage box
can organize
the bottles and jars in the storage box.
To access them, just pull out the storage box to take them out.
It is convenient and can effectively use the space.
Use a fresh-keeping bag to freeze and distribute them. You
can use a storage box to put similar ingredients together.
When cooking, it is better to find
the bag with the storage time marked on it
to avoid putting the ingredients in the expired
freezer. There are many bags of group buying ingredients
stacked together, often forgetting its existence
. The expired
file rack can also be used for storage in the refrigerator.
This kind of bagged ingredients can be stored upright
and can be pulled out directly
to take it out. It is very convenient.
If you accidentally buy a file rack that is too large,
you can also place it horizontally in the refrigerator
to directly store beverage bottles Don’t be afraid that
the cans wo n’t be able to stand upright.
Everyone should have a lot of
unprocessed fruits and vegetables
in paper bags . You can use paper bags as compartments
to keep them organized and keep them moisturized.
Choose clean paper bags that are
a little thicker and more
durable .
If the paper bag gets wet and dirty, just throw it away and replace it with a new one.
If the refrigerator has a separate vegetable and fruit room,
you can use a storage box to separate the space for the vegetable and fruit room.
Put the bags of vegetables and fruits vertically
instead of stacking them horizontally so that you can find
fish bought from the vegetable market. 1. After the seafood
is cleaned and sorted
, put this kind of flat fresh-keeping box or fresh-keeping bag,
and
then put it in the freezer
to
refrigerate and
keep
fresh. After the amount is
put flat, put it in the refrigerator
and freeze it. When you use it, you don’t need to defrost it.
You can take out
the ground meat
you want to use without
defrosting it. Silicone molds
can also be used for packaging.
Silicone molds can be heat-resistant -20~240 degrees. It
is very suitable as a separation layer for packaging.
Put the ground meat in silicone molds and put them in
a crisper and
put them in the freezer for storage.
Baking paper is also divided Packed
Costco cheese is a big package every time you buy it.
If you open the package and don’t eat it quickly,
it will soon become moldy.
Divide the cheese into small portions and freeze it
to extend the shelf life. Divide
the cheese into small portions before freezing. Use
baking paper to wrap each serving separately
and put them back into the original zipper bag
for frozen storage. You should choose the
baking paper for freezing and subpackaging.
There will be signs on
the packaging that can be used for freezing.
There are endless cakes How to store it?
Don't use plastic wrap to ruin the beautiful decoration on the cake,
you can replace it with a fresh-keeping box
Turn the box upside down
, put the cake on the lid,
then cover it and
put it in the refrigerator for storage.
Not only is
it easy to take the cake, but
it is also very complete.
The most important purpose of
organizing the refrigerator
is to manage the ingredients
. It will be put in the forgotten stack until it expires.
Now start to store your refrigerator properly.
Do you have this problem too?
Clothes obviously don't look much but there is always not enough space?
The wardrobe is messy like a warehouse.
Clothes are stuffed in boxes.
After emptying the
wardrobe, reorganize the wardrobe space.
Coats and long tops
are sorted out and then hung on the wardrobe hangers
.
Drawer storage boxes can be used to increase storage space
between the hanging clothes and between the shelves. Do you fold your clothes in half and then in half like this?
Stacked in drawers or cabinets.
Every time I take clothes, I have to rummage for a long time. When
I find the clothes, I take them out and the drawers are messed up.
Don’t use this method to collect clothes anymore.
Standing clothes upright
makes it easier to organize and save space.
Store clothes upright . It is easier to find and hold. If
you want to stand up the clothes,
you need to adjust the folding method
. The easiest way
is to fold all the clothes into squares
and put them in the drawer. They can stand up well without falling over. Divide
the clothes into three equal parts.
Fold the left and right sleeves to the middle,
then fold the hem and neckline first,
and finally fold it from bottom to top
so that the pattern of the folded clothes
will be visible outside
and the clothes can stand upright on the table
neatly after folding In addition
to the tops, trousers can also be stored upright.
Folding techniques for organizing clothes - trousers square folding method
First put the bottom of the trousers away and fold the trousers to the same width.
The trousers are folded in half first
and then folded into a square
shape The basic concept of clothes is the same.
If it is a one-piece dress,
you can first fold the dress in half
, then fold the skirt into
three equal parts,
and then divide it into three equal
parts again , and put the two sides inward on one side
to complete
the one-piece dress. Hang it up directly. It will be too long and take up space
. Prepare two hangers
. Put the hangers into the collar
, then draw the clothes into thirds
and put another hanger through the skirt.
Finally, hook the lower hanger to the upper hanger
to complete
the soft sweater. It can be stored upright.
Fold the sleeves inward first,
and then
fold the clothes into thirds to form a rectangle.
This is a short version of the sweater,
so we divided it into thirds,
and finally tucked the neckline side into the other side to complete it.
If you want to hang the sweater
so
that it hangs on
the
shoulder side, it is easy to have marks.
You
can change the method to
hang the
sweater. Out of shape
. The storage of socks is also very important.
First flatten the heel of the sock
, then fold the heel to heel together,
then divide
the sock into three equal parts , and then
insert
the toe part into the sock opening
. Grab the toe of one of the socks
and then grab the other sock
and pull it in
to complete
the last fold. For long socks,
first flatten the heel part, overlap
the two socks crosswise
, and then fold the bottom socks Cross and overlap upwards
, then cross and overlap the upper socks once
and stuff them into the opening of the socks
to complete.
Fold the socks in double
and use the storage box to store them neatly.
The socks can also
be stored upright in a roll
. Stacking and storing in the cabinet
can also be DIY to create a hat storage area in the closet.
The curtain ring clip and the telescopic rod
hat have hanging space.
Compared with the stacking method,
it is more convenient to use
the ring clip. We bought
a 12 yuan
from Shopee. There is this kind of "universal hook clip"
with a relatively large opening
, and the hair cap is not afraid of being scratched.
It is cheap and easy to
use. The universal hook clip can rotate 360 ​​degrees
and can be hung upside down to
store sundries
and hang bags. You
can also use this kind The large-sized divider
can stand upright to store bags, shopping bags, etc.
When you go out, you can quickly match
the open shelf
with the
Oita grid
to store the bags here.
If the bag
is placed on the ground or on the window sill
for a long time, it will cause the space to be messy.
You can hang the mesh next to the gate
and match the hook with the grid rack
to place the keys
. The masks for epidemic prevention, hand washing and other
perforated boards can be used at the entrance.
It is a good choice to place the things that will be used in daily entry and exit.
If there is a place in the entrance,
it is a good choice to set up such a large-faced perforated board.
The distance between the hooks can be arranged according to the needs,
and different lengths of laminates can be added to store different items.
We Use the concept of a daily wardrobe to design the location of the items.
The coats you wear every day and the bags you need to go out
are placed in a
place close to the door that is easy to pick
up Put the disinfection alcohol on
the top part of the board
. We use two wooden sticks to help store the electric mosquito swatter.
While using the space,
it can also prevent children from accidentally being shocked by electric shocks. Bills,
letters, etc.
can be arranged at the entrance for a letter sorting area
for storage . Pens, scissors, and utility knives
for signing and unpacking
are convenient for taking out
letters from mailboxes. The letters taken out of the mailbox can also be sorted and placed upright.
Bills that need to be paid
can be attached to the door
with magnets or clips to remind yourself
to avoid forgetting
. As the 3C devices at home are getting more and more Most
of them are mobile phones, mobile power supplies, electrical appliances, and batteries.
Charging lines one at a time and one at a time are really unsightly.
It is better
to build a 3C device charging station
to solve the mess caused
by a pile of charging lines and sockets on the desktop It
looks messy.
This problem can be solved with a hook.
For example, the wires of an electric fan can be hung with two hooks,
one facing upwards and the other facing downwards,
and glued to the back of the electric fan
. Remember that the spacing should not be too close
to ensure enough Use the hook
to store the wires in the space. You can also use the hook to store
the wires neatly . In the bedroom and study space,
you can use a strong magnet to store
the strong magnetic adhesive strips, and
you can easily store small iron objects
such as nail clippers, tweezers, and fretwork. Needles, etc.
are lined up neatly
, beautiful and easy to find.
You can also use this set of IKEA "Magnetic Knife Holder"
which was originally used on the kitchen wall.
You can clearly see all the knives
and easy to pick up.
The characteristics of magnetic suction are also very suitable for hanging storage
. A pile of messy charging cables
Just stick the magnetic knife holder on the edge of the table or the wall
and fix
it with non
-marking glue
Cosmetics
can make good use of pegboard
Replacing the function of the cosmetics cabinet,
this is a perfectionist
laminate with perforated board accessories. It
is also very convenient to take care products and cosmetics.
The perforated board of IKEA is also very convenient to install
bottles and jars. If they are all placed on the table,
it will definitely look beautiful
Put the makeup foundation, powder, lipstick, etc. on the shelf in a mess. Leave
the maintenance supplies on the table.
Separate the items with different functions and
take them. It will become very intuitive
and you don’t need to rummage
in the bathroom. With the perforated board, you can easily store a lot of things.
Use a whiteboard marker to assist positioning
and match the non-marking screw stickers to fix the perforated board on the wall
. On the layer, we put relatively dry toothpaste and cleaning supplies
. Below it, use the hook to hang it Bath balls and other relatively wet items,
if you are afraid of using habits, it will cause water accumulation on the laminate.
Toothpaste and facial cleanser can also be clamped with this clip with a hook and
matched with an elastic lanyard to
hang it to facilitate drying without fear of water accumulation.
Because the bathroom is the most humid place in the home,
pay special attention to the material when choosing perforated boards.
Avoid choosing wooden perforated boards
,
otherwise
it is easy to get moldy
. It is sticky and
should not be installed in a place where it is easy to splash water.
The above share 35 easy and fast storage methods.
After watching the video, which method is your favorite?
Welcome to discuss with everyone in the message area.
Those who have not followed the ig of Wajia
can click on the upper left If you like today's sharing,
please
click "Super Thank you" below
to support us in making more practical videos.
Any intractable diseases
are welcome to leave a message or send a private message
to follow IG to see secret techniques
. Join the club and various experts will help you
in the end . Remember to like, subscribe
, and turn on the little bell
to lock Frog House. Every Wednesday update
will bring you a high-quality content that will make your life better.